Experimental College Records UA044
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Course files, 1965 -- 2012; UA044.003; 22.8 Linear Feet
  - EXP 21F, Fall 1983 (EXP 21S, Spring 1984): Horses and Horsemanship, Jeff Katz and Phyllis Albritton, 1983 -- 1984; UA044.003.020.00049 (Box 20)
  - EXP 21S, Spring 1982: Jazz: History and Aesthetics, Steve Elman, UA044.003.020.00050 (Box 20)
  - EXP 21F, Fall 1978: Music: a Voice of Social Change, Rachael Worby, UA044.003.020.00051 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1989: Americans in Paris: Post-WWI Writers and the Avant Garde, Donna Hollenberg, UA044.003.020.00052 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22F (FR 001X), Fall 1988: En France Comme Si Vous Y Etiez, Christiane Fabricant, UA044.003.020.00053 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1988: The American Museum, Gail Hercher, UA044.003.020.00054 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1987: Words and Images out of Vietnam, Frieda Gardner, UA044.003.020.00055 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22F, Fall 1987: Japanese Popular Culture, Frances Seeds, UA044.003.020.00056 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22F, Fall 1986: At the Crossroads: A Look Forward, Ron Kertzner, UA044.003.020.00057 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1986: Fire and Rain: America 1960-1975, Roseanne Allexenberg, UA044.003.020.00058 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1984: Hazardous Waste Assessment, Wayne Chudyk, Lewis Edgers, and Annette M. Rossignol, UA044.003.020.00059 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22F, Fall 1982: Duke Ellington and Charles Mingus: Jazz History Through the Composer's Eye, Steve Elman, UA044.003.020.00060 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1979/Spring 1980/Fall 1987: Introduction to Electronic Music Synthesis, Robert DiCamillo, 1979 -- 1987; UA044.003.020.00061 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1979: Fundamentals of Electronic Music, Robert DiCamillo, UA044.003.020.00062 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22F, Fall 1979: Introduction to Computing, George Stalker, UA044.003.020.00063 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1977: Introduction to Modern Irish, Kenneth Nilsen, UA044.003.020.00064 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22S, Spring 1976: Introduction to Dutch, Su Van Stolk, UA044.003.020.00065 (Box 20)
  - EXP 22F, Fall 1976: Japanese Language, Makoto Yamazaki, UA044.003.020.00066 (Box 20)
  - EXP 23F, Fall 1989: French in Motion, Carolyn Fidelman, UA044.003.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - EXP 23S, Spring 1988: The Utopian Novel: a Legal/Social Perspective, Gianna Biondi and John Copeland, UA044.003.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - EXP 23S, Spring 1982: Introduction to Folk Music, Nancy Mitchell, UA044.003.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - EXP 23S, Spring 1981: Basic Sign Language, Barbara Krieger, UA044.003.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24F, Fall 1988: A History of Hysteria, Gillian Gill, UA044.003.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24S, Spring 1987: Writing and the Arts in Contemporary Ireland, Susannah Lee, UA044.003.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24F, Fall 1987: Cross-Cultural Studies, Theresa Smith, UA044.003.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24S, Spring 1986: The Anthropology of Fiction, Kerry Skiffington, UA044.003.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24F, Fall 1986: Architecture, Shaping Urban Form, Yim-Lei Lim, UA044.003.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24S, Spring 1985: Computer Revolution? Mechanization Culture and Everyday Life, James Ennis, UA044.003.021.00010 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24S, Spring 1984: Energy for Survival, Nathaniel Hecht, UA044.003.021.00011 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24S, Spring 1983: Pascal, David Schatsky, UA044.003.021.00012 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24F, Fall 1981: Advanced FORTRAN Programming, Howard Mendel, UA044.003.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24S, Spring 1979: Sight-singing and musicianship, John Duffy, UA044.003.021.00014 (Box 21)
  - EXP 24F, Fall 1976/Spring 1978/Fall 1980: American Sign Language, Terrell Clark, 1976 -- 1980; UA044.003.021.00015 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25F, Fall 1989: TV-Popular Culture, Nancy Abelmann and Philip Setel, UA044.003.021.00016 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25S, Spring 1989: Kibbutz, David Leichman, UA044.003.021.00017 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25F, Fall 1985: Elementary Korean I, Kyungyon Kang, UA044.003.021.00018 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25S, Spring 1984: Modular Transportable Programming, Richard Mann and Christina Willrich, UA044.003.021.00019 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25S, Spring 1983: Cobol, William Greenberg, UA044.003.021.00020 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25S, Spring 1980: Scientific Programming Using Pascal, James Cooper, UA044.003.021.00021 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25F, Fall 1978/Spring 1981: American Sign Language, Terrell Clark, 1978 -- 1981; UA044.003.021.00022 (Box 21)
  - EXP 25F, Fall 1976: Word Play, Marjorie Pedersen, UA044.003.021.00023 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26F, Fall 1988: Cults: Dealing with Destructive Religion, Robert Thornburg, UA044.003.021.00024 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26S, Spring 1988: Proportion in the Living World: Natural, Architectural and Theatrical Forms, Rachel Fletcher, UA044.003.021.00025 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26F (DR 193 D), Fall 1986: Porportion and Harmony in the History of Theatre Architecture, Rachel Fletcher, UA044.003.021.00026 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26S, Spring 1986: Vodoun Culture: Reality of a Caribbean Island, Rachel Beauvoir, UA044.003.021.00027 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26S, Spring 1985: Experimental Archaeology, John Merkel, UA044.003.021.00028 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26S, Spring 1984: Introduction to Computers, Daniel Dennett and David Isles, UA044.003.021.00029 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26F, Fall 1983: Introduction to Computers, George Smith and James Schlessinger, UA044.003.021.00030 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26F, Fall 1979: Advanced MACRO Planning, Bill Meier, UA044.003.021.00031 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26S, Spring 1978: Intermediate FORTRAN, William Lober and Susan Reilly, UA044.003.021.00032 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26F, Fall 1976: Advanced MACRO Programming, Bill Meier, UA044.003.021.00033 (Box 21)
  - EXP 26S, Spring 1976: Persian I, Khosro Toofanian, UA044.003.021.00034 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27F, Fall 1989: American Folklore, Eleanor Wachs, UA044.003.021.00035 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27S, Spring 1987: Popular Music and the Rise of an American Youth Culture, Steven Stark, UA044.003.021.00036 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27S, Spring 1986: Yankee Catholicism, Michael Hunt, UA044.003.021.00037 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27F, Fall 1984: Emergency Response, Mary Sturtevant, UA044.003.021.00038 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27S, Spring 1983: Biochemical Revolutions and Revolutionaries, Bill Brennan, UA044.003.021.00039 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27F, Fall 1982: Structured PASCAL Programming, Marc Michault, UA044.003.021.00040 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27S, Spring 1981/Spring 1982: Introduction to COBOL Programming, Peter Chatzky, 1981 -- 1982; UA044.003.021.00041 (Box 21)
  - EXP 27F, Fall 1977: Advanced MACRO, David Ackley, UA044.003.021.00042 (Box 21)
  - EXP 28S, Spring 1989: Life and Love in 12th-Century France: the Legacy of Heloise, Eleanor, and Marie, Priscilla Baumann, UA044.003.021.00043 (Box 21)
  - EXP 28F, Fall 1986: Cells, Selves, and Strangers: Writing Intensive Seminar, Stephen Bailey, Susan Ernest, Steven Hirsch, and Howard Woolf, UA044.003.021.00044 (Box 21)
  - EXP 28S, Spring 1984: Introduction to Horticulture, Mark Wourms, UA044.003.021.00045 (Box 21)
  - EXP 28F, Fall 1983: Statistics and Computing, Robert Houser, UA044.003.021.00046 (Box 21)
  - EXP 28S, Spring 1980: Evolutionary Astronomy, Gordon Weinblatt, UA044.003.021.00047 (Box 21)
  - EXP 29S, Spring 1987: Pornography in American Culture, Janice Irvine, UA044.003.021.00048 (Box 21)
  - EXP 29S, Spring 1985: Between Language and Thought: Cultural and Psychological Perspectives, Carol McCleary, UA044.003.021.00049 (Box 21)
  - EXP 29F, Fall 1984: Clinical and Experimental Aphasiology, Susan Kohn, UA044.003.021.00050 (Box 21)
  - EXP 29F, Fall 1982: Advanced MACRO Programming, David Schatsky, UA044.003.021.00051 (Box 21)
  - EXP 29F, Fall 1981/Spring 1983: Introduction to the Biology of Birds, Barney Schlinger, UA044.003.021.00052 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30S, Spring 1990: Taking Intiative, Francie Chew, UA044.003.021.00053 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30S, Spring 1987: Images of Women in the Judeo-Christian tradition, Myriel C. Eykamp, UA044.003.021.00054 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30F, Fall 1986: Living in Your Body: How It Works and What it Does, Janice Irvine and Peggy Barrett, UA044.003.021.00055 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30S, Spring 1985 (EXP 39S, Spring 1986): Disorders of Desire: The Politics and Ideology of Sex Experts in American Culture, Janice Irvine, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.003.021.00056 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30S, Spring 1985: Korean Culture, Kyungyon Kang, UA044.003.021.00057 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30F, Fall 1983: Toward Adulthood: Developmental Issues Facing the College Student, Praxedis Mayr von Baldegg, UA044.003.021.00058 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30F, Spring 1981/Fall 1986: Introduction to Immunology, Osama M. Kandil, 1981 -- 1986; UA044.003.021.00059 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30F, Fall 1980/Spring 1987: Computer Structure and Function, Charles Bartlett, UA044.003.021.00060 (Box 21)
  - EXP 30S, Spring 1979/Fall 1979: The Plight of the Male, Fredric Hayward, UA044.003.021.00061 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31F, Fall 1989: Psychology of Eating Disorders, Emily Fox, UA044.003.021.00062 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31S, Spring 1987: Working with Dreams, Connie Lorman, UA044.003.021.00063 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31S, Spring 1986: Between Cultures, Adrienne Nussbaum and Jane Etish Andrews, UA044.003.021.00064 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31F, Fall 1983/Spring 1986: Cults, Persuasion, and Human Vulnerability, Joan Carol Ross, 1983 -- 1986; UA044.003.021.00065 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31F, Fall 1985: Cults, Persuasion and Human Vulnerability, Jane Carol Ross, UA044.003.021.00066 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31S, Spring 1985: Junior Year Abroad: Cross-Cultural Perceptions, Jane Etish-Andrews, UA044.003.021.00067 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31S, Spring 1984/Fall 1984: Dream Interpretation, Simone Alter and Dana Cushing, UA044.003.021.00068 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31S, Spring 1983: Across Cultures, Susan Kuder, UA044.003.021.00069 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31S, Fall 1981/Spring 1982/Spring 1983: Jewish Folklore, Pamela Adelman, 1981 -- 1983; UA044.003.021.00070 (Box 21)
  - EXP 31S, Spring 1978: The Gift, Lewis Hyde, UA044.003.021.00071 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32S, Spring 1987: Psychology of the Newly Handicapped, Tim McGowan, UA044.003.021.00072 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32S, Spring 1986: Children Through the Ages, Duane Gage Vorce, UA044.003.021.00073 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32S, Spring 1985/Spring1990: Group Decision-Making, Susan Carlisle, 1985 -- 1990; UA044.003.021.00074 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32S, Spring 1982: Mysticism, Vali Reza Nasr, UA044.003.021.00075 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32F, Fall 1981: Afro-American Religions in the Caribbean, John Homiak, UA044.003.021.00076 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32F, Fall 1979: American Cultural Perspectives, Larry Levine, UA044.003.021.00077 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32F, Fall 1977: Women, Legal Order, and Development, Shadrack Gutto, UA044.003.021.00078 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32S, Spring 1978: The Sea, Jay Kaufman, UA044.003.021.00079 (Box 21)
  - EXP 32S, Spring 1976/Spring 1979: Asian-American Roots, Liz Toupin, 1976 -- 1979; UA044.003.021.00080 (Box 21)
  - EXP 33F, Fall 1984: Decision-Making, Susan Carlisle, UA044.003.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - EXP 33F, Fall 1983: Families with a Difference: Coping with Mental Illness, Susan Phelps, UA044.003.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - EXP 33S, Spring 1983: American Ways of Death, Michele Theresa Di Palo, UA044.003.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - EXP 33F, Fall 1982: Access to the Mainstream: Planning Programs for People with Disabilities, Janet Kamien, UA044.003.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - EXP 33F, Fall 1982: Creative Opportunities for Individuals with Disabilities, Amy Goldbas, UA044.003.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - EXP 33F, Fall 1981: Asian-American Roots, Elizabeth Toupin, UA044.003.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - EXP 33S, Spring 1977: Asian American Issues: Two Personal Experiences, David Shimbo and Selina Jung, UA044.003.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - EXP 33S, Spring 1976: U.S. Popular Culture, Randy Feldman, UA044.003.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34S, Spring 1989: Incest in American Culture, Kerry Skiffington, UA044.003.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34F, Fall 1985/Spring 1987: Group Dynamics, Michael Basseches, 1985 -- 1987; UA044.003.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34F, Fall 1985: Stress, Coping, and Social Support, Mary Moran, UA044.003.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34S, Spring 1984: Competition: the Need to Be Number One, Alfie Kohn, UA044.003.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34S, Spring 1983: The Psychology of Romantic Love, Praxedis Myar von Baldegg, UA044.003.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34F, Fall 1981: A Celebration of Difference, Martha Chew, UA044.003.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34S, Spring 1979/Spring 1980: Black Woman in America, Patricia Hill Collins, 1979 -- 1980; UA044.003.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34F, Fall 1979: A Woman's Education: Options and Dilemmas, Polly Kaufman, UA044.003.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34S, Spring 1978: Creativity and Imagination, Oliver Hoffman, UA044.003.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - EXP 34S, Spring 1976: UFOs: Fact and Fiction, Jonathan Earle, UA044.003.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35F, Fall 1989: Dynamics of Leadership, Marcie Kelly and Cathy Harder-Bernier, UA044.003.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35S, Spring 1986: Exploring Womens' Issues, Jane Park and Lauren Weinberg, UA044.003.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35S, Spring 1985: Exploring Womens' Issues, Kate Burchett and Beth Zallinger, UA044.003.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35, Summer 1985: Dynamics of Group and Organizational Behavior, Bruce Greenspan, UA044.003.022.00022 (Box 22)
    also includes material related to summer 1985 courses taught by Howard Woolf and Nancy Dietz
  - EXP 35S, Spring 1984: Women's Speech: Language and Sexual Identity, Nancy Smith-Hefner, UA044.003.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35S, 35F, Spring/Fall 1983: Violence in the Home, Sandra Vallery, UA044.003.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35S, Spring 1979: The Psychology of Cults, William Onifer, UA044.003.022.00025 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35F, Fall 1978: Parenting in the '80s, Olga Baloueff, UA044.003.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35S, Spring 1978: Workshop in Family History, Leila Joseph, UA044.003.022.00027 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35S, Spring 1977: Decision Making: Case Studies and Models, Thomas Winant, UA044.003.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35F, Fall 1976 (EXP 71S, Spring 1979): Marketing Strategy and Decision Analysis, Diane Hessan-Tackeff and David Poldoian, 1976 -- 1979; UA044.003.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - EXP 35S, Spring 1976: Entrepreneurship, Richard Klavans, UA044.003.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36F, Fall 1987: Leadership and Life in Groups, Virginia Thorndike Hules, UA044.003.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36F, Fall 1984: Childcare in the U.S., Marion Nesbit, UA044.003.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36S, Spring 1984/Spring 1986: Rights and Responsibilities: Relationships, Marriage, and the Law, Norma Villarreal, 1984 -- 1986; UA044.003.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36S, Spring 1983: Thicker than Water: Parent-Child Relationships, Fred Rothbaum, UA044.003.022.00034 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36S, Spring 1982: Sexuality, Relationships, and Contraception, Peggy Barrett, UA044.003.022.00035 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36F, Fall 1981: The Hotline Experience, Mary Block, Jane Ginsburg, and Beth Leventhal, UA044.003.022.00036 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36S, Spring 1981: Women's Roles in Judaism, Betsy Cohen, UA044.003.022.00037 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36S, Spring 1980/Fall 1980: Issues in Modern American Health Care, Sara Mattes and Joan Stern, UA044.003.022.00038 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36S, Spring 1979/Fall 1979: Comparative Anthropology of China and Japan, Grant Rhode, UA044.003.022.00039 (Box 22)
  - EXP 36S, Spring 1976: Food Service and Restaurant Management, Dino Romano, UA044.003.022.00040 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37F, Fall 1988/Spring 1989: Stress Management, Elizabeth Dolan, 1988 -- 1989; UA044.003.022.00041 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37S, Spring 1986: Explorations in Leadership, Daniel Mulhern, UA044.003.022.00042 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37F, Fall 1985: Women to Women: Building Bridges, Jerma Jackson and Victoria Nunez, UA044.003.022.00043 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37F, Fall 1982/Spring 1983: Age, Aging, and the Elderly in Contemporary America: A Workshop, Herb Patchell, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.003.022.00044 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37S, Spring 1982: Introduction to Peer Counseling, Bryant Churn, UA044.003.022.00045 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37S, Spring 1981; Women and Health, Marisa Messore, UA044.003.022.00046 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37S, Spring 1979: Applications of Psychology in Contemporary Society, L. Dodge Fernald, UA044.003.022.00047 (Box 22)
  - EXP 37F, Fall 1978: Violence Against Women, Susan Flint, UA044.003.022.00048 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38F, Fall 1987/Spring 1988: Sexuality Informational Theatre, Janice Irvine, 1987 -- 1988; UA044.003.022.00049 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38S, Spring 1985: Hags, Witches, Sirens: Images of Women in 16th-Century Northern Europe, Jane Carrol, UA044.003.022.00050 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38S, Spring 1984: Exploring Women's Issues: a Study Group, Stacy Brustin, Robin Kaplan, and Sarah Novagrodsky, UA044.003.022.00051 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38S, Spring 1983: Love and the Human Person, Father Tom Foley, UA044.003.022.00052 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38F, Fall 1980/Spring 1981: Beginner's Guide to Ending Hunger, Charles Deull, 1980 -- 1981; UA044.003.022.00053 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38S, Spring 1980: The Education of the Gifted Child: Who, What, and Why?, Constance Stolow, UA044.003.022.00054 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38S, Spring 1979/Fall 1979/Spring 1980: The Mother-Daughter Relationship, Carol Lambert, 1979 -- 1980; UA044.003.022.00055 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38S, Spring 1978: Intercultural Communication, Leslie Long, UA044.003.022.00056 (Box 22)
  - EXP 38F, Fall 1977: Workshop: Intercultural Communication, Meg Little, UA044.003.022.00057 (Box 22)
  - EXP 39F, Fall 1984: Contemporary Issues of Black Women, Susan Frazier-Kouassi, UA044.003.022.00058 (Box 22)
  - EXP 39S, Spring 1983: Men, Women and Power, Michele Bograd, UA044.003.022.00059 (Box 22)
  - EXP 39F, Fall 1982: Coming to Terms with an Intolerant World, Gordon Gottlieb, UA044.003.022.00060 (Box 22)
  - EXP 39S, Spring 1981: Herbs and Natural Foods, Hollis Greenspan, UA044.003.022.00061 (Box 22)
  - EXP 39S, Spring 1979: The World We Create, Penny Prather, UA044.003.022.00062 (Box 22)
  - EXP 40S, Spring 1984: War, Conflict and Violence, Rob Elias and Maryanne Wolf, UA044.003.022.00063 (Box 22)
  - EXP 40S, Spring 1981: The Psychology of Eating Disorders, Cathy Raduns, UA044.003.022.00064 (Box 22)
  - EXP 42F Fall 1976 (EXP 40F Fall 1977/Fall 1978): Building a Personal Philosophy of Life, Bob Miller, 1976 -- 1978; UA044.003.022.00065 (Box 22)
  - EXP 41S Spring 1990: Introduction to Peace and Justice Studies, Paul Joseph, UA044.003.022.00066 (Box 22)
    folder is labled as "EXP 41PS"
  - EXP 41F, Fall 1987/Spring 1988: Toward a Just World Order, Gerald Gill and Frieda Gardner, 1987 -- 1988; UA044.003.022.00067 (Box 22)
  - EXP 41F, Fall 1986: Toward a Just World Order, Paul Joseph and Maryanne Wolf, UA044.003.022.00068 (Box 22)
    folder is labled "EXP 41PF"
  - EXP 41F, Fall 1985: Toward a Just World Order, Robert Elias, UA044.003.022.00069 (Box 22)
    folder is labeled "EXP 41PF" folder is labeled "EXP 41PF"
  - EXP 41F, Fall 1984: Toward a Just Society, P. Joseph, UA044.003.022.00070 (Box 22)
    folder is empty of materials
  - EXP 41S, Spring 1983 (EXP 41F, Fall 1983): Toward a Just Society, Robert Elias, UA044.003.022.00071 (Box 22)
  - EXP 41S, Spring 1982/Fall 1982/Spring 1983: Foundations and Treatment of Stress and Anxiety in American Society, Leighton Reynolds, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.003.022.00072 (Box 22)
  - EXP 41F, Fall 1981: Stress Management, Randy Kamen, UA044.003.022.00073 (Box 22)
  - EXP 41S, Spring 1978/Spring 1979: Simple Lifestyles, Tom Boland, 1978 -- 1979; UA044.003.022.00074 (Box 22)
  - EXP 42S, Spring 1988: Advanced Seminar, Peace and Justice Studies, Paul Walker, UA044.003.022.00075 (Box 22)
  - EXP 42F, Fall 1986: Social Movements and Social Change Organizations, Dale Bryan, UA044.003.022.00076 (Box 22)
  - EXP 42S, Spring 1986: Utopias and Dystopias, Tim Allen, UA044.003.022.00077 (Box 22)
  - EXP 42S, Spring 1985: Religion, War and Peace, Richard Groves, UA044.003.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - EXP 42F, Fall 1984: The Anthropology of War and Peace, Bette Denich, UA044.003.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - EXP 42S, Spring 1984: Practical Visions of a Non-Violent World, Jane Guise and Nancy Brink, UA044.003.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - EXP 42S, Spring 1980/Spring 1983: The Hiroshima and Nagasaki Experience, Tadatoshi Akiba, UA044.003.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - EXP 42S, Spring 1981/Spring 1982: Seminar in American History, Gray Graffam, 1981 -- 1982; UA044.003.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - EXP 42S, Spring 1978/Spring 1979/Fall 1980/Spring 1981/Spring 1982/Spring 1983: Architectural Planning According to a Land Ethic, Frederick Hamlen, 1978 -- 1982; UA044.003.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43F, Fall 1988: Black Women in Protest, Marcelyn Dallis, UA044.003.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43S, Spring 1987: Race and Law in the U.S. and South Africa, Brian Blaney and Paul Weisenfeld, UA044.003.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43F, Fall 1985/Fall 1986: Famine in Africa and International Response, John Constantelos, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.003.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43S, Spring 1985: Issues in Domestic and Global Refugee Policy, Stephen Golub, UA044.003.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43S, Spring 1984: Human Rights in Latin America, Beatriz Manz, UA044.003.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43F, Fall 1983: What Will it Take to Prevent Nuclear War?, Pat Farren, UA044.003.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43S, Spring 1983: War and Peace in the Nuclear Age, Jerome Grossman, UA044.003.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43F, Fall 1981: Gossip and its Effect upon Community, Jeffrey Summit, UA044.003.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43S, Spring 1981/Fall 1981/Spring 1982: Prisons: Reality vs. Myth, Joyce Freedom, 1981 -- 1982; UA044.003.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43S, Spring 1980/Fall 1980: Gypsies, Leita Kaldi, UA044.003.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43F, Fall 1978/Fall 1979: Designing Environments, Hisham Ashkouri, 1978 -- 1979; UA044.003.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43S, Spring 1978: Urban Awareness and its Development, Alexandros Samaras and Dimitri Balamotis, UA044.003.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - EXP 43F, Fall 1977: History of Astronomy, Earl Wajenberg, UA044.003.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44F, Fall 1989: Homelessness in the U.S., Rachel Bratt, UA044.003.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44S, Spring 1987: Psychology of Nuclear Issues, Sarah Conn, UA044.003.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44S, Spring 1986: The Kibbutz of Today, Michal Pagli, UA044.003.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44S, Spring 1985: Advocacy, Participation, and Public Issues, Georgia Mattison, UA044.003.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44F, Fall 1984: Human Rights Advocacy, Diana Bell, UA044.003.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44S, Spring 1984: From Anti-Fascism to Anti-Communism, Jerry Meldon, UA044.003.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44S, Spring 1981: Deschooling and Non-Traditional Education, Donald Gratz, UA044.003.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - EXP 44S, Spring 1980: Iranian Culture, Shahriar Moin, UA044.003.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - EXP 45S, Spring 1989: Facing History, Steven Cohen, UA044.003.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - EXP 45F, Fall 1988: Homosexuality in America, Donna Penn, UA044.003.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - EXP 37S, Spring 1980/Fall 1980/1981 (EXP45): Cooperation: A Necessary Step, Carol Swann, UA044.003.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - EXP 45S, Spring 1979: Indian Philosophy, Elizabeth Mullens, UA044.003.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - EXP 45S, Spring 1978: Parapsychology, Mark Dickstein, UA044.003.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - EXP 46S, Spring 1980: Values and the Person, Guillemine de Lacoste, UA044.003.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - EXP 46F Fall 1978: Chemistry Around Us, Frank Guziec, UA044.003.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - EXP 46S, Spring 1978: Physics and Mysticism, Adrian Segar, UA044.003.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - EXP 46S, Spring 1977: Fourth Level Thinking, Gordon G. Evans, UA044.003.023.00036 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47S, Spring 1989: Discriminiation and Its Remedies in American Life, Law and Theory, Douglas Schwarz, UA044.003.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1987/Spring 1988: Developing a Liberating Theology, Graylan Ellis-Hagler, 1987 -- 1988; UA044.003.023.00038 (Box 23)